Please save my mommy.
- Yvette.
- Andrew, it's mom.
They said mommy
is in the hospital.
Go see her.
Clarissa, why did you
leave her alone?
I can't handle it if something
happens to Ma'am Rebecca.
Wait, why did mommy overdose?
- It looks intentional.
- She couldn't do that.
Do you believe what Tomas said?
All of these are
just assumptions.
Your Korean friend,
do you still talk to him?
Who? Jin Ho?
That's not his real name
and he's not Korean police.
Does it bother you that you're
still not part of us?
I want to be in the room
where decisions are made.
Now, I'm burning bridges
for this organization!
Berdugo doesn't show himself
to ambition.
You want to meet him?
Prove you can wait.
You and Lisa will handle
the operations for now.
So, you'll make it look like
suicide?
Yes, that way there's
no complications.
Given her condition
and medications,
authorities will read it
as trauma or psychosis.
Tomas...
I'll call you back.
Thank you.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew, what do you need?
Is that the hospital?
The what?
My sister told me
you were suggesting
a better hospital for mom.
Yes, a specialist.
Better equipped,
more experienced.
I only want the best
for your mother's team.
Thank you, Tomas.
I'm really appreciative that...
you're doing this for mommy.
You don't have to thank me,
Andrew.
We're family, remember?
Tomas, you and Yvette
should go home.
I'll watch over mommy.
No, I'll stay.
The doctor might arrive.
I need to speak
to her personally.
I'll just have the driver
take Yvette home.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom, why? Who's that?
One of the maids at the mansion.
She said Ma'am Rebecca
is comatose.
Mom, don't overthink too much.
No, dear.
But you know,
what I'm thinking is,
Ma'am Rebecca isn't depressed.
Yes, she was often not
in the mood but not depressed.
Well, Mom, people can't really
assume that
because no one saw what really
happened.
What are you doing?
Can I help?
This...
It's a spy camera attached to
the eye of the stuffed animal.
The teddy bear...
Teddy bear?
Yes, child.
In Ma'am Rebecca's room,
she had a teddy bear,
and it had a spy camera.
I'm sure it recorded
what really happened.
It would be good if we could get
that footage.
Yes.
Nanny, tie up the trash bags.
Yes, Ma'am.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
The brown stuffed bear I gave
her for her birthday...
can I see it?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mommy?
Sweetheart...
Don't come here.
It's dusty, child.
Is grandmother coming home
already, Mommy?
Not yet, dear, but...
if you pray harder, maybe.
How about Aunt Clarissa?
Is she coming back when
grandmother comes back?
Wait, child, okay?
I just have to do something.
Should I tell Ma'am Yvette?
But, Mom,
we're not sure if the camera
in the teddy bear
recorded anything.
You're right.
I don't want to add
to Ma'am Yvette's worries.
But I'll just ask one of the
maids at the mansion for help.
[PHONE RINGING]
It's Ma'am Yvette.
Answer it, but relax, Mom, okay?
Ma'am Yvette...
Hello, Clarissa?
How are you?
I'm fine, Ma'am.
We're still waiting
for mommy to wake up.
Clarissa, I've been thinking.
I'm sorry.
I was too emotional.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry I shouted at you.
Ma'am, don't worry.
I understand. It's normal...
when something bad happens
to someone we love,
we look for someone to blame.
It happened to me too.
Thank you.
Do you want to visit mommy?
Yes, of course.
All right.
We transferred her
to another hospital,
so I'll just text you
the address.
Okay.
Ma'am, can I stop
by the mansion first?
I left some things
in Ma'am Rebecca's room.
Okay.
I'll tell the maids
you're coming.
All right, thank you, Ma'am.
I'll also get some clothes
for Ma'am Rebecca
to bring to the hospital.
Okay, thank you, Clarissa.
Thank you, Ma'am.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
The tip I got said
most of the people who have
their cars cleaned here
are Koreans,
because the owner is Korean.
I just thought...
Why would he go here?
It's all Koreans.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Because at the carwash,
they only notice the cars,
not the people.
What's your plan, Major?
Are you going inside?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you sure it was here
when something happened
to Ma'am Rebecca?
Yes, I last saw it here,
but I don't know why it's gone
now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
So? Did you find
what you were looking for?
Ma'am, well...
Did you notice
a brown stuffed toy?
A teddy bear.
The one for Kisses?
Yes, yes.
I saw it earlier
when I was cleaning.
It was thrown in the trash.
What?
This is where we threw
the trash.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is it?
Are you sure you only throw
the trash here?
Yes, just here.
Why is there no trash now?
Maybe the garbage truck
passed by.
Why would they throw you away?
Good thing I found you
right away.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stay here first,
so no one can see you.
I won't let anyone
throw you away.
Bye.
It surely went straight
to the dump.
If you go there,
you'll have a hard time
searching.
It's big, and it stinks.
- But if you want...
- No need.
It's okay. Thank you.
All right. I'll leave you now.
I'll go back to what
I was doing.
- Thank you.
So, what now, Mom?
Did Ma'am Rebecca tell you
why she put a spy camera?
[STAMMERS]
Yes, but I couldn't...
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Right, I remember now.
It's a spy camera attached
to the eye of the stuffed toy.
There's someone I need to catch.
It needs to end
before my family gets hurt.
Is that true, Mom?
Child, why would I lie?
I clearly remember because
when she told me that,
I was so confused
about who she wanted to catch.
The problem is,
I didn't get to ask her.
Why?
Did you notice anything unusual
about her?
Maybe she has an enemy?
The maids?
No, the maids were kind.
Then who could it be?
Ma'am Yvette?
Sir Tomas?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Cruz,
is he there?
Negative, Major.
Not here either. It's hard,
they all look alike.
I told you, Major.
Just wait there.
If he'll try to escape.
We can chase him.
Hello.
Indonesia?
[STAMMERS]
Vietnamese?
- Filipino.
- Yes.
I knew it!
Even if we're in the
Philippines,
there are no Filipinos here.
Mostly foreigners.
You like the coffee, Sir?
Yes.
Nice! You know what?
You're gonna love it
because we have a service.
It's unlimited.
Anytime, you can come
to have a drink, Sir.
Don't Filipinos love coffee?
Yes.
I'm going to eat.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
[CLAPS]
A Filipino client here!
It's been so long!
Yes, Sir!
- Okay, very good. Here, Sir.
- Thank you!
What was that, Major?
Be careful, Major.
You might draw
too much attention.
Remember...
The syndicate thinks
you're dead.
Focus on the shop.
Standby there, okay? Stay alert.
Did Ma'am Rebecca tell you
not to trust Sir Tomas?
Why?
I don't know...
She kept warning me.
A person too private...
usually has many secrets.
Just remember...
Do not trust Tomas.
What do you think, dear?
Should I tell Ma'am Yvette?
Anyway, we're okay now.
But, Mom, it's risky.
He's still Ma'am Yvette's
husband.
And we don't have
a solid evidence.
True.
Ma'am Rebecca
is in comatose too.
She can't confirm anything
I say.
What if...
You tell Sir Andrew instead?
I'm sure he'll understand.
It's for his mother.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
She's been a doctor
for 25 years.
She specializes
in neurocritical care,
so she can give us
the right explanation
about your mother's case.
I reviewed Rebecca's case
thoroughly...
And she suffered a prolonged
hypoxic episode
due to drug toxicity.
The damage is significant.
But she's stable, right?
Medically, yes.
But recovery isn't just about
stability.
She has reflexes, yes,
but no meaningful response.
You mean she has no chance
of waking up?
Of course, there is.
But the longer she remains
unresponsive,
the narrower the chance becomes.
Thank you, Doc.
We appreciate your honesty.
I'll leave you for now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Get some rest.
The nurses are watching over
your mother.
Let's go?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew.
Leave him be. Let's go.
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom,
wake up please.
I know you can hear me.
I know that you always could
even when you didn't want to.
That's what you always
told me before, right?
You always sense things
and you always know
what's happening around you
even when you pretended not to.
That's why I know...
you couldn't do this
to yourself, Mom.
You're brave, aren't you?
You don't give up.
This isn't you, Mom.
This doesn't make sense.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cruz,
they're almost done cleaning
my car.
Still no Jin Ho.
Are you sure your informant
said he hangs out here?
He wouldn't give weak intel,
Major.
Maybe the target just isn't
coming here today.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR CHIMES]
Why are you following me?
Are you a pervert?
Are you gay?
No, no.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho...
Where did he go?
I don't know if...
I should start working.
Because...
I just keep overthinking.
But I can't focus.
Just call me when you need
someone to talk to, okay?
And don't worry about
the "Tirada," Boss.
I can do what you do too.
Look.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm Kyle Cañete,
striking for the truth.
[CHEEKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Anytime, anywhere.
That was good, right?
See? Right?
How do you do it it again? How?
Again, again, again.
[ELAI LAUGHS]
I'm cooler
by about 5 points, Boss.
All right.
You only dream once
in a while anyway.
[KYLE CHUCKLES]
So, you agree?
We'll lose our subscribers.
Hey, wow, harsh.
They'll increase.
They'll grow to 1 million.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hi, guys.
- Hello.
- Hi, Zoey.
All right, Andrew,
we'll go ahead.
- Text us.
- Boss...
Me, okay?
- Take care.
- Boss, what I said, okay?
Start moving.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
How are you?
How's Auntie?
How did you know?
From Yvette.
You know, Andrew,
just because we broke up
doesn't mean I cut off all your
connections in my life.
And...
When I heard what happened
to Auntie Rebecca,
I knew you needed someone.
That's why I'm here.
I'm here.
Just like before when something
happened to her too.
No, you weren't there.
You left.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Honestly, it's so hard
to see our mother like that.
Good thing I'm not alone.
My children are here...
Tomas, and of course, Andrew.
When I started thinking that...
maybe mommy did think of doing
this to herself...
but thank God,
Andrew was able to knock
some sense into me.
Because he's the one who knows
mommy better.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am, is Andrew here now?
Yeah, he's in the garden.
I'll just go see him. Excuse me.
All right.
You, Clarissa,
do you think mommy
could commit suicide?
Ma'am...
There's...
There's something I should
tell you.
Yvette.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Clarissa.
What were you going to say,
Clarissa?
Is everything okay?
Yes, Sir.
Nothing, Ma'am.
What I was going to say
isn't important.
I'll just say it another time.
All right.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't forget my advice, okay?
I won't be like you.
What's this?
I got it from inside there.
Can you help us,
Uncle Andrew?
Okay, what is this?
Let's see.
Yvette, I still can't imagine
how this happened to mommy.
I know for myself she couldn't
do this to herself.
So, who? Who would do this?
The only reason I agreed
to come with you
is to see if Jin Ho
is still here.
Emman!
This is about your friend,
Jin Ho.
He's a criminal.
If he's been in the syndicate
for a long time,
why doesn't his name appear
in our files?
Come.
It's not impossible
for the syndicate to doubt
as long as they don't see
your body.
We'll stand by the claim
that I'm dead.